[Music]
hey and welcome I'm hammy and in this
series we're discovering the law
backstory and characters of overwatch's
Heroes including more detail through
their in-game voice lines and
interactions before any map starts and
during the game on various triggers
OverWatch Heroes chatter with and react
to each other in some funny in-game
voice interactions these give us some
great insights into hero character
interests and backstories this video
we're looking at junkrat's story through
his interactions with fellow heroes or
villains and the world around him an
explosive obsessed freak who lives to
cause chaos and destruction junkrat is
currently on the run with his partner in
crime Road Hog causing chaos Around The
World Slightly radiation tinged and
unhinged from his time as a junker
junkrat holds a valuable secret that
bounty hunters and nefarious individuals
are hunting him for whether we'll find
out what it is in time remains to be
seen firstly we'll quickly run through
junkrat's story the first omnic crisis
affective lives all around the world
when defunct dismantled omnian massive
factories of automated construction
machines and self-improving software
algorithms built by the omnica
corporation decided to wake themselves
back up they launched a military
campaign against all of humanity
Australia wasn't sped in the peace
agreements following the crisis
government officials gifted the
Australian omnium and the surrounding
area to the omnic that nearly destroyed
their country hoping to establish a
longtime piece oford this Arrangement
permanently displaced a large number of
the Outback's residents a scattered
collection of survivalists solar farmers
and people who just wanted to be left
alone Furious over the loss of their
homes this group turned to Violent
Rebellion events escalated until the
rebels sabotaged the omniums fusion core
resulting in an explosion that destroyed
the facility IR radiated the region and
led the Outback with Twisted Metal and
wreckage for kilometers around some
people survived calling themselves the
junkers they scavenged the husk of the
omnium and formed a lawless Cutthroat
Society in its shadow junkrat was one of
them he eak out a living by reclaiming
metal and components from the ruins like
many others he was affected by the
lingering radiation this touch of M
Madness made him ideal for handling
dangerous explosives Al love which he's
turned into a bit of an obsession it's
safe to say junkrat would have just been
another casualty of the war if he hadn't
shot to notoriety when he discovered an
extremely valuable secret in the bones
of the Australian omnium few know the
nature of what he's found but he was bed
by bounty hunters gangs and opportunists
wherever he went until he struck a deal
with the junker enforcer Road Hog Road
Hog grudgingly bodyguards junkrat in
exchange for a 50/50 share of the spoils
probably the only reason he puts up with
the explosive obsessive now with road
hog and Tow junkrat has left the Outback
and embarked upon an international crime
spree leaving nothing but havoc and
bedum in his wake so far we've seen the
pair in the UK and Kings Row stealing
the crown jewels robbing in a vat in
Dorado Mexico and even breaking into ice
cream trucks in Paris and robbing arcade
toys in what might be hanamura Japan we
also know that junkrat and Road Hog have
been to Sydney as detailed in their
comic going legit at some point when
what they thought was a legitimate job
turned out to be a setup they got an
explosive Revenge with the presumed
death of the CEO or a senior member of a
company called hide Global as well as
destroying a building in Sydney's
Central business district even with a
motto of no job too big no score too
small is there any reason for this trail
of Destruction in Mayhem does it have
anything to do with the treasure that
junkrats hiding or are the two just well
enjoying themselves with this mad pair
you probably can't tell it's a perfect
day for some Mayhem as you might expect
for a crazy explosive obsessive jrat
loves nothing more than talking about
his favorite hobby and that of course is
blowing things up you look like the kind
of guy who could use something blown up
it's hard to just sit around knowing
there's someone out there that needs to
be blown
up if at first you don't succeed blow it
up
again a don't mind me I was just taking
five definitely not thinking about
blowing something up no way definitely
not okay come on maybe just a little
something and when he's not talking
about his vocation junkrat's doing his
second favorite thing or things in the
world those are cracking bad jokes and
throwing insults I've got to leg up on
the competition but just
one don't you come the raw prawn with
me aiming is
overrated out of my face you drungo
while we're on the subject of bad jokes
junkrat loves to mock just about
anything and anyone stay tuned for a
mini junkrat quiz can you guess what
junkrat is taking the mick out of in
each of these lines I'll give the
answers after each one baby I'm a
firework that of course is ktie Perry
with her fireworks song and on that
bombshell that's of course his Top Gear
Jeremy Clarkson's old sign off line at
the end of every
episode now that's a
knife the infamous knife scene in
Crocodile Dundee when they compare the
size of their knives if I had a PhD
they'd call me Dr boom of course that's
Dr boom from Area 52 nether storm in
World of Warcraft and since known as Dr
balance or Dr 7 in Heartstone time is
money friends and we're almost flat
broke attack
time is money friend is a direct
reference to goblins in World of
Warcraft they say it all the time when
you click on them now the last one of
these is really impressive thanks to our
guest voice over for spotting this one
where do you think this music is from or
how it's referring to
[Music]
junkrat now I don't think that's in game
but according to our guest voice over
it's in Via Vendetta and Hugo weaving
actually wears a guy Forks mask
throughout the film this music is used
in the final scene where the houses of
Parliament get blown up spoiler do of
course remember that junk rack's name is
Jameson Forks guy Forks blowing stuff up
finally this music is also used in some
fireworks displays and you see fireworks
with music so multiple different
references there in that little bit of
music very very cool cheers to our guest
voice over for spawning that one junkrat
and Road Hog by knowing each other don't
have huge connections with the other
cast of OverWatch at the moment but that
does not stop junkrat from liberally
chatting to and in some cases mocking a
lot of them as we know junkrat and Road
Hog are literally as thick as thieves
Road Hogs in it for the money guarding
junkrat for a half share of his treasure
and the two make quite the double act on
some some occasions junkrat has a very
literal view of the pair's relationship
sometimes you hook them I'll cook them
and when Road Hog asks junkrat to stay
out of trouble junkrat swears he will
maybe Road Hog's the Father Figure in
this team up I'll be on me best behavior
apparently Road Hog comes out with the
joke even according to junkrat you won't
believe the joke old pig face over there
told me the other day a road hog
ultimately though we know Road Hog's a
man a few words when junkrat sees an
Allied Road Hog get a kill on his team
he expresses his thanks I knew there was
a reason I kept you around and it wasn't
the sparkling conversation whatever
barbs he throws Road Hogs away junkrat
does care about the fate of his
bodyguard when a road hog gets killed on
the same team as a junkrat you might be
able to hear this line I think hey I'm
the only one who gets to kill the big
lug and I have no idea when this line
triggers but it's kind of touching for
junkrat to say this to Road Hog don't
you think I could always count on you
mate junkrat has a few interactions with
may even if he's trying to be polite and
make conversation May doesn't really
want to have anything to do with him I
get cold just looking at you they us
should look somewhere else and when may
criticizes junkrat his usual wit comes
to his defense take your own pun
medicine May you're just a no good bully
how can you even look at yourself in the
mirror that's cold as one of the faces
of OverWatch Tracer is a prime target
for junkrat's quips even her trademark
catchphrase isn't safe cheers mate the
cavalry's here that's my line now
junkrat probably regrets his rudeness
when his curiosity about explosives gets
the better of him think I could have a
look at one of those bombs of yours now
as we've seen from his bio junkrat's no
fan of omnic and I think this line
triggers when he either gets hit or
Discord orb from an enemy zata there's a
couple of variations piece of junk
junkrat even finds it funny when he sees
one of himself he looks familiar hey
that's me finally I'm not sure of the
trigger for this or if it's in game but
it's kind of interesting to see how
junkrat sees himself anyway I beg your
pardon I consider myself a freedom
fighter a misunderstood one in the last
of our interactions there's a couple of
interactions with other Heroes around
junkrat's treasure now I don't have the
lines on me but Hanzo and apparently
Reaper both ask him about his treasure
with Hanzo saying You couldn't possibly
keep it on your person apparently
junkrat has a couple of responses to the
two different individuals here's one of
them where did you hide your treasure
you could hardly have it on your person
treasure sure I don't know anything
you're talking about when it comes to
the world of OverWatch we know that
junkrat and Road Hog from their crime
spree are pretty well traveled since
leaving the Outback so naturally
junkrat's got a bunch to say on several
Maps the tension between omnic and
humans in King's Row strikes a chord
with junkrat he's of course had tensions
with omnic in his own life too here's
what he says when he spawns on King's
right so we're delivering a bomb to
scrap some Bots and I'm getting paid for
it my kind of job and equally as we've
seen in a moment in crime the video
about junkrat and Road Hog the two
actually stole the crown jewels or
definitely did some kind of heist here
and both of them more reminisce fondly
about it in a couple of different ways
ah remember that time we stole the crown
Jewels all hail King Jameson Forks the
first and uh Duke rhog what is your name
anyways God Save the
King Nani of course is meant to be the
city where omnics and humans live
together in harmony and junkrat
naturally is a little bit skeptical to
say the least about this this place is
the worst let's turn it into one big
Scrappy really no fan of omnic as we can
see several times dado is quite closely
linked to junk and Road Hog there's a
whole bunch of evidence showing that
they've robbed the bank their faces on
the monitors here for example the bank
heist map in the level that was also
shown at BlizzCon 2015 I think in the
law panel and the sprays of jungr and
Road Hog if you're very quick that you
can see in soja 76 is hero short on this
wall for my review of that short check
out the video on the channel link below
of course when junkrat returns to the
scene of the crime he does have a little
reminisce and maybe wonders if he needs
a little bit more liquid cash assets
should we say hey me old tunnel might be
time to make another withdrawal
junkrat's no fan of omnic as we've seen
in his comic and in other lines so
visiting the home of the chambaran in
thepole is naturally not going to be to
his liking at all there's a couple of
different lines associated with here
when junkrat spawns and maybe another
one I think as well if these Bots want
to go into the light I'd be more than
happy to help now this place makes me
want to be an atheist whatever his
feelings towards omx junkrat always
defaults back to his trademark uh
entrepreneurship he sees the business
opportunities on the Temple of annabis
sure enough when spawn in as you should
be able to hear here you think there's
something worth stealing in that Temple
junkrats always appreciative of fellow
Craftsman when I say Craftsman I mean
people who can create chaos and
destruction and I think that this one
may well be on Route 66 when he's
looking at the rec track wow look at
this m hat off to the architect of this
fantastic destruction and finally for
fun not heard this but perhaps it's when
junkrat passes one of the coffee shops
in game has anyone heard this one can
you do a flat white no how b i flatten
the place thanks very much for tuning in
to my hero voice line and Story series
check out the playlist linked here on
the left for more videos like this of
different Heroes if you like this video
please hit that like button subscribe
comment share it on social and let me
know what you thought what lines you
enjoyed most and any Heroes you'd like
to see covered next I really appreciate
hearing what you all think until next
time I've been hammy take it
[Music]
easy
bit of an obsession it safe to say
junkrat would have just been another
casualty of the war if he hadn't shot to
notoriety when he discovered an
extremely valuable secret in the bones
of the Australian omnium few know the
nature of what he's found but he was
pursued by bounty hunters gangs and
opportunists wherever he went until he
struck a deal with the junker enforcer
roadhog Road Hog grudgingly bodyguards
junkrat in exchange for a 50/50 share of
the spoils probably the only reason he
puts up with the explosive obsessive now
with Road Hog in toe junkrat has left
the Outback and embarked upon an
international crime spree leaving
nothing but havoc and bedum in his wake
so far we've seen the pair in the UK and
King's Row stealing the crown jewels
robbing in a vault in Dorado Mexico and
even breaking into ice cream trucks in
Paris and robbing arcade toys in what
might be hanamura Japan we also know
that junkrat and Road Hog have been to
Sydney as detailed in their comic going
legit at some point when what they
thought was a legitimate job turned out
to be a setup they got an explosive
Revenge with the presumed death of the
CEO or a senior member of a company
called hide Global as well as destroying
a building in Sydney's Central business
district even with a motto of no job too
big no score too small is there any
reason for this trail of Destruction in
Mayhem does it have anything to do with
the treasure that junkrat's hiding or
are the two just well enjoying
themselves with this mad pair you
probably can't tell it's a perfect day
for some Mayhem as you might expect for
a crazy explosive obsessive jrat loves
nothing more than talking about his
favorite hobby and that of course is
blowing things up you love look like the
kind of guy who could use something
blown
up it's hard to just sit around knowing
there's someone out there that needs to
be blown
up if at first you don't succeed blow it
up
again I don't mind me I was just taking
five definitely not thinking about
blowing something up no way definitely
not okay come on maybe just a little
thund and when he's not talking about
his vocation junkrat's doing his second
favorite thing or things in the world
those are bad jokes and throwing insults
I've got a leg up on the competition but
just
one don't you come the raw prawn with
me I'm me best behavior apparently Road
Hog comes out with the old joke even
according to junkrat you won't believe
the joke old pig face over there told me
the other day a roadhog ultimately
though we know Road Hog's a man of few
words when junkrat sees an Allied Road
Hog get a kill on his team he expresses
his thanks I knew there was a reason I
kept you around and it wasn't the
sparkling conversation whatever barbs he
throws Road Hogs away junkrat does care
about the fate of his bodyguard when a
road hog gets killed on the same team as
a junkrat you might be able to hear this
line I think hey I'm the only one who
gets to kill the big lug and I have no
idea when this line triggers but it's
kind of touching for junkrat to say this
to Road Hog don't you think I could
always care on you mate junkrat has a
few interactions with may even if he's
trying to be polite and make
conversation May doesn't really want to
have anything to do with him I get cold
just looking at you they us should look
somewhere else and when may criticizes
junkrat his usual wit comes to his
defense take your own pun medicine May
you're just a no good bully how can you
even look at yourself in the mirror
that's cold as one of the faces of
OverWatch Tracer is a prime target for
junkrat's quips even her trademark
catchphrase isn't safe cheers mate the
Cavalry is here that's my line now
junkrat probably regrets his rudess when
his curiosity about explosives gets the
better of him think I could have a look
at one of those bombs of yours now as
we've seen from his bio junkrat's no fan
of omnic and I think this line triggers
when he either gets hit or Discord orbed
from an enemies in yata there's a couple
of variations piece of junk junkrat even
finds it funny when he sees one of
himself he looks familiar hey that's me
and finally I'm not sure of the trigger
for this or if it's in game but it's
kind of interesting to see how junkrat
sees himself anyway I beg your pardon I
consider myself a freedom fighter a
misunderstood one in the last of our
interactions there's a couple of
interactions with other Heroes around
junkrat's treasure now I don't have the
lines on me but Hanzo and apparently
Reaper both ask him about his treasure
with Hanzo saying You couldn't possibly
keep it on your person apparently
junkrat has a couple of responses to the
two different individuals here's one of
them where did you hide your treasure
you could hardly have it on your person
treasure sure I don't know anything
you're talking about when it comes to
the world of OverWatch we know that
junkrat and Road Hog from their crime
spree are pretty well traveled since
leaving the Outback so naturally
junkrat's got a bunch to say on several
Maps the tension between omnic and
humans in King's Row strikes a cord with
junkrat he's of course had tensions with
omnic in his own life too here's what he
says when he spawns on King's right so
we're delivering a bomb to scrap some
Bots and I'm getting paid for it my kind
of job and equally as we've seen in a
moment in crime the video about junkrat
and Road Hog the two actually stole the
crown jewels or definitely did some kind
of heist here and both of them all
reminisce fondly about it in a couple of
different ways ah remember that time we
stole the crown jewels all hail King
Jameson Forks the first and uh Duke rhog
what is your name anyways God Save the
King Nani of course is meant to be the
city where omnics and humans live
together in harmony and junkrat
naturally is a little bit skeptical to
say the least about this this place is
the worst let's turn it into one big
Scrapy really no fan of omnic as we can
see several times dado is quite closely
linked to junkrat and Road Hog there's a
whole bunch of of evidence showing that
they've robbed the bank their faces on
the monitors here for example the bank
heist map in the level that was also
shown at BlizzCon 2015 I think in the
law panel and the sprays of jungr and
Road Hog if you're very quick that you
can see in soja 76' hero short on this
wall for my review of that short check
out the video on the channel link below
of course when junkrat returns to the
scene of the crime he does have a little
reminisce and maybe wonders if he needs
a little bit more liquid cash assets
should we say hey me old tunnel might be
time to make another withdrawal
junkrat's no fan of as we've seen in his
comic and in other lines so visiting the
home of the chambaran in Nepal is
naturally not going to be to his liking
at all there's a couple of different
lines associated with here when junkrat
spawns and maybe another one I think as
well if these Bots want to go into the
light I'd be more than happy to help now
this place makes me want to
[Music]
be hey and welcome I'm hammy and in this
series we're discovering the law
backstory and characters of overwatch's
Heroes including more detail through
their in-game voice lines and
interactions before any map starts and
during the game on various triggers
OverWatch Heroes chatter with and react
to each other in some funny in-game
voice interactions these give us some
great insights into hero character
interests and Back stories in this video
we're looking at junkrat's story through
his interactions with fellow heroes or
villains and the world around him an
explosive obsessed freak who lives to
cause chaos and destruction junkrat is
currently on the run with his partnering
crime roadhog causing chaos Around The
World Slightly radiation tinged and
unhinged from his time as a junker
junkrat holds a valuable secret that
bounty hunters and nefarious individuals
are hunting him for whether we'll find
out what it is in time remains to be
seen firstly we'll quickly run through
junkrat's story the first omnic crisis
affected lives all around the world when
defunct dismantled omnion massive
factories of automated construction
machines and self-improving software
algorithms built by the omnica
corporation decided to wake themselves
back up they launched a military
campaign against all of humanity
Australia wasn't Spar in the peace
agreements following the crisis
government officials gifted the
Australian omnium and the surrounding
area to the omx that nearly destroyed
their country hoping to establish a
longtime piece oford this Arrangement
permanently displaced a large number of
the Outbacks residents a scattered
collection of survivalists solar farmers
and people who just wanted to be left
alone Furious over the loss of their
homes this group turned to Violent
Rebellion events escalated until the
rebels sabotaged the omniums fusion Corp
resulting in an explosion that destroyed
the facility IR radiated the region and
ltered the Outback with Twisted Metal
and wreckage for kilometers around some
people survived calling themselves the
junkers they scavenged the husk of the
omnium and formed a lawless Cutthroat
Society in its shadow junkrat was one of
them he eak out a living by reclaiming
metal and components from the ruins like
many others he was affected by the
lingering radiation this touch of
Madness made him ideal for handling
dangerous explosives love which he's
turned into aing
overrated out of my face you Dro while
we're on the subject of bad jokes
junkrat loves to mock just about
anything and anyone stay tuned for a
mini junkrat quiz can you guess what
junkrat is taking the mick out of in
each of these lines I'll give the
answers after each one baby I'm a
firework that of course is ktie Perry
with her fireworks song and on that
bombshell that's of course his Top Gear
Jeremy Clarkson old signoff line at the
end of every
episode now that's a
knife the infamous knife scene in
Crocodile Dundee when they compare the
size of their knives if I had a p HD
they'd call me Dr boom of course that's
Dr boom from Area 52 nether storm in
World of Warcraft and since known as Dr
balance or Dr 7 in Hearthstone time is
money friends and we're almost flat
broke
attack time is money friends is a direct
reference to goblins in World of
Warcraft they say it all the time when
you click on them now the last one of
these is really impressive thanks to our
guest voice over for spotting this one
where do you think this music is from or
how it's referring to
junkrat
now I don't think that's in game but
according to our guest voice over it's
in Via Vendetta and Hugo weaving
actually wears a guy Forks mask
throughout the film this music is used
in the final scene where the houses of
Parliament get blown up spoiler do of
course remember that junk rack's name is
Jameson Forks guy Forks blowing stuff up
finally this music is also used in some
bioworks displays and you see fireworks
with music so multiple different
references there in that little bit of
music very very cool cheers to I guess
voice over for spawning that one junkrat
and Road Hog by knowing each other don't
have huge connection with the other cast
of OverWatch at the moment but that does
not stop junkrat from liberally chatting
to and in some cases mocking a lot of
them as we know junkrat and roadhog are
literally as thick as thieves Road Hog's
in it for the money guarding junkrat for
a half share of his treasure and the two
make quite the double act on some
occasions junkrats has a very literal
view of the pair's relationship
sometimes you hook them I'll cook them
and when Road Hog asks junkrat to stay
out of trouble junkrat swears he will
maybe Road Hog's the Father Figure in
this team up I'll be